

Vishal Mehta

Sr. UI/UX Designer

PROFILE OVERVIEW

Skilled User Interface & User Experience Designer with experience of 4.5+ year. Currently Responsible for UI & UX Design for Flights Channel: An Travel Agency provide flight ticket booking at cheap price. I help brands in achieving their users' and business objectives. Expertise in user-friendly user interfaces. & experience, design systems, prototyping, wireframing, Dashboard Designing & Report Prepration.

EXPERIENCE

Sr. UI/UX Designer

Flights Channel

Apr 2023 - Present

Flights Channel is a travel agency. They Provides Flights Ticket at cheap price. Here my responsibility to make the website user friendly and improve user interface also responsible for CRM portal.

UI/UX Designer

Mobile Programming LLC.

July 2021 - June 2022

Mobile Programming proviedes Digital Transformation Services. Mobile Programming's various end-to-end digital solutions include - Metaverse/AR/VR, Internet of Things, Cloud Computing, Progressive Web Apps etc. Here my work is to make app or website user-friendly and provide better user experience to the user and client satisfaction. I'm Directly interact with the clientts. I was worked there for US Clinets on multiple projects.

UI/UX Designer

Pristyn Care

Jan 2021 - July 2021

Pristyn Care is a new-age healthcare company with a laser-sharp focus on simplifying the entire surgery journey of a patient and his/her attendant by offering care and assistance at each and every step. Here I was responsibile for multiple products like Dashboard, App & website. I worked their in team we make their products for internally team and also for the user. I was responsibile for solving the user probem they facing and design better User interface and user and improve user experience.

Graphics & UI/UX Designer

Aakarist Pvt. Ltd.

Aug. 2018 - Dec. 2020

Aakarist is a services provider agenct it provides for online platform. I started aakarist as a graphics designer & it end as as became UI UX Designer. I was direct interacting with the clients and responsible for the end to end design process. I worked on multiple projects.

PERSONAL

vishalmehta216@gmail.com +91 86839 45421

SKILLS

UI Design

UX Research

Product Design

Prototyping

Visual Design

Wireframing

Design System

Interaction Design

Dashboard Design

User-centered design

Graphics Design

■ TOOLS

Figma

Adobe XD

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Photoshop

Zeplin

■ EDUCATION

Bachelor of Technology

Manav Rachna International University 2014-2018

Senior Secondary

Haryana Board of School Education 2011-2012

Secondary

Haryana Board of School Education 2010-2011

■ CERTIFICATION

Google UX Design Professional Certificate

Coursera

Credential ID 348NJGBNQDV7

■ LANGUAGE

English

Proficient

Hindi

Proficient